mutualofomahabank.com 2016-11-24

# Privacy Policy - Mutual of Omaha Bank

**  
On-Line Privacy Policy**

Mutual of Omaha Bank (“Mutual of Omaha”) respects the privacy of visitors of mutualofomahabank.com, mutualofomahaebank.com and all sites linking to this On-Line Privacy Policy (“Policy”) (collectively “sites”). This Policy explains how Mutual of Omaha collects, uses and shares information about you from our sites and the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected, used and shared. Mutual of Omaha encourages you to read this Policy and those of all web sites you visit.In addition to this Policy, Mutual of Omaha’s written Consumer Privacy Notice further describes how we handle your personal information (defined below) shared with us, such as when you apply for or purchase our services. If you would like to view this Privacy Notice, please click on the link below: 

  * Consumer Privacy Notice 

The following sections address our sites’ on-line privacy practices in more detail: 

####  Sites covered by this Policy

This Policy applies to all services and sub-sites available under the domains mutualofomahabank.com mutualofomahaebank.com and all sites owned or operated by Mutual of Omaha or its affiliates linking to this Policy. We encourage you to read our Policy before using the sites. By visiting our sites, you are agreeing in advance to the current and future terms of this Policy. If you do not wish to agree to these terms, you should leave this web site. 

####  Types of information collected on our sites

There are two types of information collected on our sites: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. 

####  Personally Identifiable Information 

#### Personally Identifiable Information (“personal information”) is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mailing address, email address, age range, etc. Personal information is only obtained when you voluntarily provide the information to us. Mutual of Omaha does not, nor do we permit any other party, to collect personal information from our sites’ visitors over time and across third party web sites. 

####  Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“non-personal information”) is information that does not identify you as an individual, such as your browser type, IP Address, and the URL of the previous web site you visited. Mutual of Omaha may automatically collect certain types of non-personal information from you when you use our sites. We may also collect non-personal information that you voluntarily provide, such as information included in response to a questionnaire or survey. 

####  Why we collect your information

Mutual of Omaha uses personal information it collects on our sites to better understand your needs and interests and to provide you with services and features that better meet your needs or requests. We only collect information that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

####  How we collect information

Mutual of Omaha collects on-line data when you provide information to us or through the use of web technology (an example would be form submissions). 

####  Information Collected Through You

If you choose to use certain services on our sites, we may require you to provide contact and identity information. Where possible, we indicate which fields are required and which fields are optional. If you choose not to use a particular service or feature, you do not have to provide the requested contact or identity information. 

####  Non-Personal Information Collected Through Technology 

####  Cookies: 

Our sites may use cookie technology to improve your experience and gather data for web site statistical reporting. Cookie technology does not capture your individual email address or any personal information about you. 

A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web site that is saved on your hard disk by your computer’s browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience (i.e., rotating images on our sites’ home pages) and gathers web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the Internet provider’s domain name and country that our visitors come from and the addresses of sites visited immediately before and after coming to our sites. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual and is measured only in aggregate. 

To browse without cookies, you can configure your browser to reject all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the “Help” menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

####  IP Address: 

Our sites may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, server problem diagnosis and compiling aggregate information, such as how many visitors accessed our sites. When you visit a particular web page on our sites, our servers log your IP address. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the Internet. We also collect IP addresses for authentication purposes when you submit on-line applications for our services. 

**Embedded Pixels:**

We may use embedded pixel technologies on selected pages for the purposes of identifying unique user visits to our sites as opposed to aggregate hits. In addition, embedded pixels or other technologies may be used in emails to provide information on when the email was opened to track marketing campaign responsiveness. Information collected using these technologies may be associated with the recipient's email address. 

####  Who we share personal information with

In the normal course of business, we may share personal information you provide to us on our sites among Mutual of Omaha and its affiliated companies, including our insurance affiliates and with select third parties as permitted or required by law. Please see the Consumer Privacy Notice in the link above for more information on how Mutual of Omaha may share information with affiliates and third parties.

**Disclosure of personal information for legal purposes and protection of Mutual of Omaha and others:**

We also reserve the right to share your personal information with third parties if we believe such action is necessary in order to: (a) conform with the requirements of any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request; (b) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our sites or our users; or (c) investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person or violations of the terms and conditions of using our sites. 

####  Your choices and opting out 

Except where we are required or permitted by law to share your personal information, you have the right to instruct us not to share your personal information. For more information on these privacy choices, see the Consumer Privacy Notice link above. 

####  Children’s privacy

Unless otherwise specified, our sites are not directed toward children. We do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that personal information on a child under the age of 13 is collected, we will delete that information from our systems. 

**Keeping your information secure**

The security of your personal information is very important to us, and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. We have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that Mutual of Omaha has collected from you through our sites. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Mutual of Omaha cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our on-line products or services, and you do so at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the sites. 

**Acceptance of Policy**

By visiting our sites, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Policy, and we have the right to use your information as described in this Policy. 

This Policy applies only with respect to the information that we collect on-line on our sites and not to any information that Mutual of Omaha collects through other methods or sources. 

If for some reason you believe that our sites have not adhered to this Policy, please notify us at one of the addresses below. 

**Changes to the Policy**

Mutual of Omaha reserves the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time. Your continued use of our sites after we post any changes to this Policy on our sites will constitute your acceptance of those changes, so please check the Policy periodically for updates.The latest revision to this Policy occurred in July 2014. Changes to this Policy will not affect our use of previously provided personal information. 

**Contacting us**

Please note that whenever you submit any information to us in connection with any Mutual of Omaha services, you consent to Mutual of Omaha’s processing of this information as necessary to provide the services in which you are participating. 

If you have any questions or comments about our **Privacy Policy** and/or the way it affects you, please feel free to contact us by: 

  * Sending an e-mail request to [webmasterbank@mutualofomahabank.com](mailto:webmasterbank@mutualofomahabank.com)
  * Sending a letter via US Mail to:

> Mutual of Omaha Bank 
> 
> Mutual of Omaha Plaza 
> 
> Omaha, NE 68175 
> 
> Attention: Web Master 

For all other general Customer Service issues please email [Bank.CustomerService@mutualofomahabank.com](mailto:Bank.CustomerService@mutualofomahabank.com?subject=Customer%20Inquiry).
